ssm-einfo.my 2015-04-06

# SSM e-Info ver 2.9 - Home (Best viewed with IE7 & Mozilla Firefox)

Thank you for using SSM e-Info Services. 

**Your Privacy** **  
** This page explains our privacy policy which includes the use and protection of any information submitted by users. 

If you choose to register and transact using our Portal or send an e-mail which provides personally identifiable data, this data maybe shared with SURUHANJAYA SYARIKAT MALAYSIA so as to serve you in the most efficient and effective manner.  An example might be in terms of resolving or addressing complaints that require escalation to SURUHANJAYA SYARIKAT MALAYSIA. 

**Data Protection**   
Leading technologies including encryption software is used to safeguard any data given to us and strict security standards are maintained to prevent unauthorised access. 

**Storage Security**   
To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured and stored with appropriate security technologies. 

**Information Collected**  
No personally identifiable information is gathered during the browsing of SSM e-Info Services except for information given by you via e-mails and registration in e-Account. 

**Feedback**   
We welcome all feedbacks/inquiries via email to [callcenter@ssm-einfo.my](mailto:callcenter@ssm-einfo.my) or by voice call to +603 4045 8686. 

In case of detailed information which the Portal may not be able to provide, your feedback/enquiry will be escalated to SURUHANJAYA SYARIKAT MALAYSIA for clarification. 

**Cookies**  
Certain websites generate ‘cookies’, which are collected by web-servers to enable them to recognise your future visits. 

The SSM e-Info Services uses only ‘non-persistent cookies’ or ‘per-session cookies’ which serves technical purposes like switching the languages of the Portal. These cookies do not permanently record data and they are not stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted. 

**What Happens When I Link to Another Site?**  
This privacy statement applies only to our site and you should be aware that other sites linked by the Portal may have different privacy policies and we highly recommend that you read and understand the privacy statements of each site. 

**Changes to this Statement**   
If this privacy statement changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties. 

**Queries or Complaints**   
If you have any queries or complaints about this privacy statement or about the Portal, you can contact us via our Feedback section.
